privatter.net 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Privatter

## Privacy Policy

As described below, we will establish personal information protection policy, establish a mechanism for personal information protection, and promote the protection of personal information by thoroughly recognizing the importance of personal information protection and efforts. 

* * *

####  Collecting personal information 

This site collects user information in the following way. 

  1. Twitter account information (screen name, profile, user name, etc.) used to register to this site 
  2. Your name, email address, Twitter account etc. you enter at the time of inquiry 
  3. E-mail address you will register to receive notifications from this site 

* * *

####  Purpose of using personal information 

We will manage personal information you keep from the user properly, and will use it to contact you and information from this site, to respond to questions. 

* * *

####  About handling personal information 

This site properly manages the personal information deposited from the user and does not disclose personal information to a third party unless it falls under any of the following. 

  1. If you have consent 
  2. When we disclose to a contractor our company outsourges to do the desired service 
  3. When it is necessary to disclose based on laws and regulations 

If you wish to inquire, modify or delete personal information of the person himself / herself, we will confirm that you are the principal and will respond. 

* * *

#### Advertising on this site

In our site, we use the services of third party ad delivery. For example, Google Adsense, i-mobile, Amazon Associates, Rakuten Affiliate and so on.

The ad serving these companies, you may order to display advertisements of products or services in accordance with the interests of the user, information about access to other sites and the site "cookie" is used. The use of Cookie, information name, address, email address, and phone number are not retrieved.

If you want to get more information about Google Adsense and the method how Cookie is not used for the advertisement delivery enterprise, please read [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html).

#### Access analysis tool

In our site, we use access analysis tool "Google Analytics" by Google.

This tool uses Cookie for collection of traffic data.  
This traffic data is collected by anonymity, and it is not a thing identifying an individual. If you want to get more information about this, please read [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html).

* * *

####  Inquiry 

For inquiries about the handling of personal information of this site from  inquiry form  thank you. 

* * *

2014/4/22 created  
2018/5/18 modified
